Guide to the Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
- Series VIII. Associations (County, State, National)- Historical Material
  - Steuben County, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Suffolk County, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Sullivan County, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Wayne County, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Wayne County, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Wyoming County Agricultural Conference Committee Report- "Planning for Tomorrow", 1945 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Wyoming County, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - CCE-County Law 224, 1973-1981 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - CCE-County Law 224, 1994-1995 (Box 58, Folder 37A)
  - CCE-County Law 224-brings funding to CCE Associations, 1994-1995 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - County Appropriations, 1918-1965 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - County Historical Records-Albany-Fulton, 1917-1966 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - County Historical Records-Genesee-Niagara, 1916-1965 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - County Historical Records-Oneida-Sullivan, 1917-1966 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - County Historical Records-Tioga-Yates, Buffalo, Rochester, Syracuse, Regional, 1917-1966 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - American Home Economics Association- Future Development Committee, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - American Home Economics Association- Future Development Committee, 1978-1988 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - American Home Economics Association- Future Development Committee, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - New York State Association of Extension Home Economists (NYSAEHE)- Award Programs, 1985-1991 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - NYSAEHE- Awards, 1956-1993 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - NYSAEHE- Board of Directors Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - NYSAEHE- Board of Directors and Membership Meeting Minutes, 1980-1987 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - NYSAEHE- Board of Directors Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - NYSAEHE- Board of Directors Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - NYSAEHE- Board of Directors Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - NYSAEHE Directories, 1987, 1990, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - NYSAEHE- Newsletter, 1985, 1986, 1989, 1990-1992 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - NYSAEHE- Procedures Handbook (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - NYSAEHE- Reports, 1986-1990 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - New York State Home Demonstration Agents Association History, 1919-1965 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - New York State Home Economics Association- Conference Packets, 1983, 1986, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - New York State Home Economics Association- Conference/Meeting Packets, 1985, 1986, 1990, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - New York State Home Economics Association- Newsletters(1980-82) Southern District Newsletter, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - New York State Home Economics Association- Membership Meeting Minutes, 1980-1989 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - New York State Home Economics Association- Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Policy Education for Families, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Policy Education for Families, 1987, 1990, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Other States
  - Farm and Home Managements Programs-Other States, 1950-1959 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Illinois- Evaluation of Educational Programs-D.M. Hill, 1956-1962 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Iowa Legislation-Realignment of Extension Service, 1955 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Iowa-Changing Farm Practices-Report of Subcommittee on Diffusion of Farm Practices of the North Central Rural Sociology Committee, 1955 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Kansas-Clarence Henry's Address at the Annual Farm and Home Week, 1935 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Kansas-Administrative (Extension) Procedure at County Levels- Prepared by L.C. Williams, 1955 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Michigan and Oregon-Extension Organization, 1950-1959 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Michigan State-Open Meetings on Agricultural Policy, 1953 (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Michigan-Administrative Reorganization of the Cooperative Extension Service, 1954 (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Missouri's Balanced Farming Program, 1946-1959 (Box 83, Folder 36)
  - Missouri-"The Genesis and Development of Balanced Farming in Missouri" A Case Study, 1954 (Box 83, Folder 37)
  - Wisconsin-National Agricultural Extension Center for Advanced Study-Robert Clark, Director, 1958-1960 (Box 83, Folder 38)
- Series IX. Photographs and Slides
  - Broome County-Treating Oats for Smut, 1911 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Fireless Cookers -Used by Mary Young and Mary Webster in Steuben County, 1917-1918 (Box 41, Folder 1A)
  - Demonstrations, Early 1900s (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Otsego County; Schoharie County-Farm Bureau Map, 1920-1929 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Chenango County Flood and School Lunch Program- Nassau County Farm Bureau, 1930-1939 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Schuyler County Flood (1937) and Wayne and Cayuga Counties, 1930-1949 (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Governor Franklin Roosevelt and Henry Morgenthau in Ithaca doing a national radio broadcast in connection with the American Country Life Conference, 1931-08-20 (Box 41, Folder 1B)
  - Unidentified people and groups, Undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified people and groups, 1946-1947 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - New York State Rural Policy Committee, Undated (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Farm and Home Special Demonstration Train, 1946 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1947-05 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1947-09 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1947-10-1947-12 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1948-01-1948-04 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1948-05-1948-08 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1948-09-1948-12 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1949-01-1949-04 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1949-05-1949-08 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1949-09-1949-12 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1950-01-1950-05 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1950-06-1950-09 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1950-10-1950-12 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1951-01-1951-05 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1951-06-1951-08 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1951-09-1951-12 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1952-01-1952-06 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1952-07-1952-12 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1956-01-1956-07 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1956-08-1956-12 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1957-01-1957-04 (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1957-05-1957-12 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication - Extension Club Retirements, 1957 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1958-07-1958-12 (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1958-01-1958--6 (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1959-01-1959-08 (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1960-01-1960-05 (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1960-06-1960-10 (Box 72, Folder 40)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1962-02 (Box 72, Folder 42)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1962-05-1962-07 (Box 72, Folder 43)
  - Photos used in "Current Episodes" publication, 1963-01-1963-02 (Box 72, Folder 44)
  - Cooperative Extension Administrative Staff, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Early Extension Work (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Thumbnails of images requested by Director Simmons, 1959 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Home Demonstration, 4H State Leaders, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Photos-painting done of Appomattox, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - John Barron and Friends - Early Extension Work (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Director M. C. Bond's Retirement, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - M. C. Burritt - Early Extension Work (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Seamon A. Knapp - Early Extension Work (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - L. R. Simms (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Director L. R. Simms' Retirement, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Director L. R. Simms' Retirement, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Director L. R. Simms' Retirement, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Director L. R. Simms' Retirement, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Director Simms' Retirement, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Carrie Taylor, 1945-1949 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Charles A. Taylor, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Three State Leaders: Wilbur Pease, Orilla Butts, Fred Morris, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Martha Van Rensselaer, Ruby Green Smith (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Agents of Change-75 Year Celebration, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Slides and Photos (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Slides- Schuyler County Model Family Resource Program (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Awareness Teaching Set-Slides and Cassette Tape (Box 66, Folder 38)
  - Natural Foods Good, Bad, Different?- slide set script by Roth Klippstein (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Come Out and Play- Slides, Script and Workbook- by Jennifer Birckmayer, Natalie Crowe, Jane Hardy, George Lavris (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - "The Inside Story of Baking. A Close Look at Cakes" - slide set script, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Be a Better Shopper- slide set (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Yeast Treats-Slide Set in English and Spanish, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 22A)
  - Menu Planning for Child Care Programs- slide set script, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Trash Tells a Tale- slide set script, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Food Quality, Food Safety and You! - slide set, 1980-1989 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Agricultural Industry: Its Impact and Future-Slides from In-Service Day, 1983-10 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Photo Contest Entries, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Photo Contest Entries, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Box 71 contains photographs from the 1940s-1980s taken by various professional photographers used in extension publications
  - Apiculture (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Birds (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Cats and Dogs (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Cattle (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Cows - Dairy (Box 71, Folder 5-7)
  - Goats (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Hogs (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Horses (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Poultry - Chicken (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
  - Poultry - Ducks (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Poultry - Turkeys (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Rabbits (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Rodents - Pests (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Sheep - Wool Production (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Corn (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Flowers (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Grain - Production (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Hay Production and Equipment (Box 71, Folder 21-22)
  - Maple Syrup (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Orchards (Box 71, Folder 24-25)
  - Produce (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Earth Moving Equipment (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Farming Equipment (Box 71, Folder 28-35)
  - Fencing (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - Irrigation (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - Logging - Tree Service (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 39-40)
  - Research-In Labs (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - Silage (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - Spraying (Box 71, Folder 43-44)
  - Structures - Buildings, Silos, Storage (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - Views, Landscapes (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - Water, Dowsing (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - Working in the Field (Box 71, Folder 48)
- Series X. Financial Records and Compliance Reviews
  - Cornell University Cooperative Extension- Records, 1944-1992 (Box 1)
    Sampling of financial records regarding the publication of the New York State Experiment Station "Bulletin" and "Memoir", published by Media Services, a Division of Extension, for the Ithaca Experiment Station
  - Federal Budgets, 1970-1988 (Box 56)
  - Federal Financial Reports, 1969-1999 (Box 56)
  - Total Expenditures, 1969-1998 (Box 56)
  - Association Audits, 1987-1989 (Box 56)
  - Association Compliance Reviews, 1995 (Box 56)
  - Association Compliance Reviews, 1995-1997 (Box 57)
  - Memorandum of Agreements, 1986-1997 (Box 57)
  - Budget/Financial Memos, 1988-1997 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - 224 State Fund Requests (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - State fiscal year folders (missing state years1941-1952;1954;1955;1957-1958;1961;1962;1967), 1939-1968 (Box 59, Folder 2-11)
  - State fiscal year folders (missing state years 1972 and 1976), 1970-1979 (Box 59, Folder 12-20)
  - State fiscal year folders, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 21-30)
  - State fiscal year folders, 1990-1994 (Box 59, Folder 31-35)
  - State fiscal year folders, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - State fiscal year folders, 1996-2001 (Box 59, Folder 37-42)
  - New York City Extension Association Law, 1957-1959 (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - 224b Area Specialists Program, 1988-1994 (Box 59, Folder 44-45)
  - CCE Budgets and Letters, 1929-1998 (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Budget and letter folders for each year, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 47-56)
  - Budget and letter folders for each year, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 57-66)
  - Budget and letter folders for each year, 1990-1999 (Box 60, Folder 1-9)
  - CCE budget requests to Deans, 1972, 1974, 1977, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - CCE System trends and other charts, 1954-2004 (Box 60, Folder 11-16)
  - CCE Association Funds History, 1929-1998 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - CCE Association letters to President - budget info, 1968-2001 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - CCE Association MOA budget info, 1966-2000 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - CCE Association letters - other than budget, 1960-1993 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Includes detailed listing of what is in folders 2-6 and 1949 report "Program of State Leaders of County Agriculture Agents", 1949-2000 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Various publications, 1960-1968 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Various publications, 1975-1978 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Various publications, 1981-1989 (Box 60, Folder 25-27)
  - Various publications, 1990-1998 (Box 60, Folder 28-29)
  - Various publications, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Regional programs, 1969-1991 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
  - Area program agreements between Cornell and CCE Associations, 1967-1990 (Box 61, Folder 3-29)
  - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax Forms (990s), 1971-1990 (Box 62)
  - Fiscal Year Plan of Work and Annual Reports
    - Plan of Work, 1961-1962 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1963-1964 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1964-1965 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1965-1966 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1966-1967 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report (Narrative Report), 1966-1967 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Annual Report (Progress Report), 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
    - Plan of Work, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
    - Plan of Work, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
    - Plan of Work, 1977-1978 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Plan of Work, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Plan of Work, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
    - Accomplishment Report (Plan of Work), 1980 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Plan of Work, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Plan of Work, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report (Accomplishment Report), 1982 (Box 10)
    - Plan of Work, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - Plan of Work, 1984-1987 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Plan of Work-ES USDA, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Plan of Work-State CRD, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Plan of Work-State, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Plan of Work, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Plan of Work-Title V, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Plan of Work-(EMIS), 1979 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Plan of Work, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Plan of Work-Counties, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Plan of Work-Federal, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Plan of Work-Narrative, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Plan of Work-New York State CRD, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Plan of Work-Narrative, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Plan of Work, 1984-1987 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Plan of Work, 1988-1991 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Plan of Work, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Plan of Work, 1992-1995 (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Plan of Work, 1992-1995 (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Plan of Work, 1992-1995 (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
    - Plan of Work, 1994-1997 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Plan of Work, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Series XI. Committees, Councils, Programs
  - Advisory Council
    - Advisory Council, 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Advisory Council-includes photos, 1987-1989 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Advisory Council, 1988-1989 (Box 85, Folder 34)
    - Advisory Council, 1990-1991 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Advisory Council, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Advisory Council, 1994-1996 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Advisory Council, 1997-1999 (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Advisory Council, 2000-2002 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Council-Membership Lists, 1970-1998 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Council-Membership Lists, 1980-2001 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Expanded Nutrition Education Program (ENEP) and Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP)
    - Cooperative Extension - (ENEP) Expanded Nutrition Education Training and Research Project with New York Medical College (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Cooperative Extension - Expanded Nutrition Education Training and Research Project with New York Medical College, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Cooperative Extension - Expanded Nutrition Education Program: Proposals from various New York State Counties, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Cooperative Extension - Expanded Nutrition Education Program: Proposals from various New York State Counties, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Cooperative Extension - Expanded Nutrition Education Program, 1960-1969 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Cooperative Extension - Expanded Nutrition Education Program, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Cooperative Extension - Expanded Nutrition Education Program, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Cooperative Extension - Expanded Nutrition Education Program, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Cooperative Extension - Expanded Nutrition Education Program, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Association EFNEP Funds History, 1969-2000 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Expanded Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP): Memos, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Expanded Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP): Memos and Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Expanded Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP): Articles, 1970-1979 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - EFNEP: Proposals, Memos, 1969-1973 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - EFNEP: Memoranda, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - EFNEP: Agents Procedures, 1970-1979 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - EFNEP: Guidelines, Philosophy, Personnel Policies, 1970-1979 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - EFNEP: South Brooklyn- Cooperative Extension, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - EFNEP: Aide Conference, 1972-06-19-1972-06-20 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - EFNEP: Progress Report (1972), Program Trends and Recommendations (1973), Situation, Scope and Priorities (1974-1975), 1972-1975 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - EFNEP: Memoranda, 1972, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - How EFNEP Helps People- New York State Case Studies, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Survey - Credit Priorities of Limited Income Families as Perceived by EFNEP Aides, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Survey-Credit Priorities of Limited Income Families as Perceived by EFNEP Aides, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - EFNEP: Brief history, testimony presented at Food Stamp Hearings by M. C. Nesheim and M. B. Washbon, Cornell University, 1976-03-25 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Certificate of Achievement for EFNEP, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Certificate of Achievement for EFNEP Teaching Assistants (Box 53)
    - EFNEP: Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program,, Nutritional Sciences, 1997 (Box 53)
  - East Harlem Nutrition Education Program
    - East Harlem Nutrition Education Program, 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - East Harlem Nutrition Education Program, 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - East Harlem Nutrition Education Program- An Exploration of Dietary Practices by Dr. Jean Bowering and Dr. Mary Morrison, 1973-09 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - East Harlem Nutrition Education Program- Dietary and Biochemical Assessment of Women in a High Risk Obstetric Clinic by Jean Bowering, Mary Morrison, Ruth Lowenberg, 1974-03 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - East Harlem Nutrition Education Program- Final Report, 1975-02 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Extension Service Summer School Program
    - Report of Committee on Summer Training Courses for Extension Workers, 1939 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Extension Service Summer School-Brochures, Photographs,Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1950-1951 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1952-1953 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1955 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1956-1957 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Extension Service Summer School, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Extension Service Summer School Photographs (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Extension Study Committee
    - Extension Study Committee, 1946-1958 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Extension Study Committee, 1946-1958 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Extension Study Committee-Final Report, 1951 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Extension Study Committee, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Extension Study Committee-Minutes, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 48)
    - Extension Service Study Committees-Discussion papers, 1963-1964 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - National Extension Homemakers Council
    - National Extension Homemakers Council Records, 1963-1981 (Box 62)
  - Potato Committee
    - Potato Committee, 1944 New York State Rural Policy Report, 1943-1947 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Potato Committee, 1948-1955 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Resilient Communities Program
    - Early Development, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Reports, Memos, 2001,2002 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Resilient Communities Program, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - CREES Project, 2002-2003 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Resilient Communities Program (1), 2002 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Resilient Communities Program (2), 2002 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Resilient Communities Program (3), 2002 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Resilient Communities Program, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Resilient Communities Program (1), 2002 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Resilient Communities Program (2), 2002 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Resilient Communities Program (3), 2002 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Final Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Resilient Communities, 2003-2005 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - 4-H